# Jorge de la Cruz Padilla

jdelacruzp7@gmail.com

📕+51 993814037 | 💌 jdelacruzp7@gmail.com | 🖸 github.com/jorgedelacruz07 | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/jorgedelacruz07

### About me

I'm a software engineer with more than 5 years of experience. I have experience with Javascript (and Typescript), Node.js and React.js. I've worked with Express.js, Koa.js and Serverless as Node.js frameworks. I built a lot of websites with Next.js and others with Nuxt.js. Also I've worked with AWS products as DynamoDB, SQS, EC2 and S3. In my first years of work, I worked with PHP (Laravel framework) and Vue.js. I like to work with Visual Code Studio, GitHub, Jira, Postman, Slack to help me to work better.

## Work Experience \_\_

Seeri Latin America

Software Engineer

Nov 2021 - Aug 2022

- I worked on a project called Seeri App. It is a general template for e-commerce projects that manage the products of the different brands that are suppliers to the client. There is a shopping cart. We are integrated with product shipping options. In addition, we have different payment method options for Mexico and Colombia.
- I worked on a project called Seeri Backoficce. It is a platform to manage sellers, suppliers, administrators, roles, products, and coupons. You can create, edit, view, and delete each element of the web. You can configure taxes, offers, categories, keywords, and attributes of each product.
- Technical Skills: TypeScript, JavaScript, Node.js, React.js, Next.js, TailwindCSS, React Admin, Material UI, Cloud Firestore

**Indra** Lima, Peru

Software Developer

Nov 2020 - Nov 2021

- I worked on a project called Rimac App Mundo which is a mobile application that helps Rimac clients to buy their vehicle and health insurance policy. The integration is based on microservices. The AWS infrastructure was used for the development of the project.
- I worked on a project called Rimac Web Salesforce. It is a web project that has integrations with Salesforce. The project is based on creating support tickets and reporting to those involved. In addition, the integrations were developed with microservices on AWS.
- Technical Skills: JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, React.js, Serverless Framework, AWS Lambda, Amazon DynamoDB, Amazon Cognito

#### Universidad Tecnologica del Peru - UTP

Lima, Peru

Software Developer

Feb 2020 - Nov 2021

- I worked on a project called Horacio. It is a website where university students can manage their schedule face-to-face and virtual, considering
  the schedules of professors, courses, and university premises.
- Technical Skills: JavaScript, Node.js, Vue.js, Nest.js, Nuxt.js, TailwindCSS, PHP, MongoDB, MySQL, Oracle.

**Joinnus** Lima, Peru

Full Stack Developer

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

- I worked on a project called Joinnus Web. The website manages the purchase of tickets for massive and small events. Different payment methods were integrated for Peru, Colombia, and Ecuador. In addition, there are benefits in each purchase of tickets for the events.
- I worked on a project called Joinnus Cashless. The cashless system is complementary to the purchase of tickets on the Joinnus web platform. This allowed the user to use points recharged on the web, within the event to purchase products without having to pay by card or cash.
- Technical Skills: JavaScript, Node.js, Vue.js, MongoDB, PHP, Laravel, Amazon SQS, MySQL, Bootstrap

Mandü Lima, Peru

Full Stack Developer

Aug 2018 - Nov 2018

- I worked on a project called Mandü Performance. This project was a website where data is filled in by companies and their employees to have metrics that help improve the company's work environment. In addition, feedback was provided based on employee performance scores.
- Technical Skills: TypeScript, JavaScript, Node.js, React.js, Serverless Framework, AWS Lambda, Amazon DynamoDB

**Prodequa** Lima, Peru

Full Stack Developer

Apr 2016 - May 2018

- I worked on a project called Isee Glasses. It is an ecommerce platform where you can buy glasses using technology that allows you to virtually try the glasses through the webcam. In addition, the lenses can be personalized. A payment gateway with Peruvian soles and dollars was integrated.
- Technical Skills: JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, Vue.js, MySQL, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB

### **Education**

#### **National University of San Marcos**

Lima, PE

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Mar 2013 - Dec 2018

British Institute Lima, PE

Advanced level Oct 2022 - currently

British Institute

Lima, PE
Intermediate level

Jan 2022 - Sep 2022

# **Projects**

**Oportunidades para todos**Lima, PE

oportunidadesparatodos.pe

• It was a project made with React.js (Next.js) on the frontend side, with Node.js (Express.js) on the backend side and we used MongoDB at the database level.

• Technical Skills: JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, Next.js, MongoDB

**Isee Glasses**Lima, PE

isee-glasses.com

- It was a project made with PHP (Laravel) on the backend side, with Vue.js (Nuxt.js) on the frontend side and we used MySQL at the database level.
- Technical Skills: PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, Vue.js, MySQL

## Skills\_

**Programming** JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, Python

Frameworks Node.js, Express.js, React.js, Next.js, Koa.js, Nest.js, Serverless, Laravel, Nuxt.js, Codelgniter

**Databases** MongoDB, MySQL, DynamoDB, PostgreSQL, Oracle

**Development Tools** Visual Studio Code, Github, GitLab, Bitbucket, Amazon Lambda, AWS S3, AWS SQS, Redis, Jenkins

**Soft Skills** Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation.